# Curriculum Vitae of Md Monir Hossain



#### Mailing Address:

House No- 88/3, Apon Nevash, Taha Road (College Road), AuchPara, Tongi, Gazipur-1230.

Cell: 01787-960556

Mail: monirhdigital@gmail.com

## Career objective:

Pursue a career in an organization where strong senses of responsibilities are very important and willing to learn and grow a valued characteristic and where the opportunity to utilize my personal qualities and experience will be available for professional career.

#### Educational background:

# SSC (Secondary School Certificate)

Name of Institute : Khali Farhat High School

Name of Board : Comilla Name of Group : Science

Result (GPA) : 3.85 (out of 5.00)

Passing Year 2014

# HSC (Higher Secondary School Certificate)

Name of Institute : Uttara Public School&

College Name of Board : Dhaka Name of Group : Science

Result (GPA) : 4.50 (out of 5.00)

Passing Year 2016

#### Bachelor of Science (Four Years Course)

Name of Institute : Tejgaon College Name of University : National University

Mejor Subject : Psychology Result (CGPA) : Appeared Session : 2017-2018

# Special Qualification:

- Ability to work under challenging, stressed, conditions & long hours.
- Ability to prepare & maintain monthly official records and reports with other documents.
- Ability to supervisions to the quality of all types finishing works.

#### Programming skills:

Office Applications : Microsoft Word & Microsoft Excel

Software : Facebook, Postman, Git & GitHub, Web Storm, Vs Code

Other : HTML, CSS3, JavaScript, React JS, Next JS, Database ORM

Prisma, MySQL

Training Institute : Ostad limited (ostad.com)

#### Employment History:

Name of Company : Super Tel Ltd

Designation : CSR-Customer Service Representative

Department : Robi Process

Duration : 10 June 2016- 31 July 2017 Location : Sector-13, Uttara, Dhaka.

Name of Company : Genex Infosys Ltd

Designation : CSA-Customer Service Associate (Premium Skill)
Department : Grameenphone inbound (121help line), social media

Duration : 15August,2017-18 June,2020

Location : NNT (06<sup>th</sup> level), Nikunjo-2, Khil khet, Dhaka-1229

Name of Company : Genex Infosys Limited
Designation : Customer Service Executive
Banglalink Social Media

Duration : 10<sup>th</sup>August,2020- 15<sup>th</sup> February,2021

Location : NNT (10<sup>th</sup> level), Nikunjo-2, Khil khet, Dhaka-1229

Name of Company : Banglalink (Third party pay roll)

Designation : Mono Brand Officer

Department : B2C & B2B Sales & Distribution
Duration : 01th March,2021 – To till now.

Job Location : Hazrat Shahjalal International Airport, Dhaka

#### Biography:

Father's Name : Md. Sirajul Islam Mother's Name : Most Husnara Begum

Date of Birth : 06/10/1997
Nationality : Bangladeshi
Religion : Islam
Marital status : Married

Permanent Address : Village- West Aoz Belia, Thana- Noakhali Sadar,

Noakhali-3800

Birth Place : Noakhali Sex : Male

Height : 5Feet 6 Inch
Weight : 58 Kgs
Blood Group : AB+

#### Language Skill:

• Bengali : Mother Toung

• English : Excellent Proficiency in Reading, Speaking, and Writing.

Md Monir Hossain Date: 05-28-2024